

Mohammad Shamsi

Back-end Developer Mobile Application Developer



Tehran, Tehran Province, Iran (+98) 9176509634

I developed a particular interest in programming during my undergraduate studies at the Computer Engineering dept., The Kermanshah University of Technology. After graduation, I worked as a freelancer for two years as an android developer. Since 2020, I

have been a Mobile Application Developer and Backend Developer

at <u>Domil.io</u> Co. My experiences made me good at independence. work and teamwork.







Work Experience



Back-end Developer · Domil.io

January 2022 - Present

In January 2022, with good experience as a mobile developer, I started a Back-end Development Position in the same team, at Domil.io company.

During this time, I have improved my skills and knowledge and had many interesting experiences.



Mobile Application Developer · Domil.io

July 2020 - January 2022

In July 2020, I started my internship as a Mobile Developer with Flutter framework. After three months, we created a new development team, and we started the Jeanswest Store Application Project. After one year and 7 months, due to personal interests and team needs, I changed my stack to back-end Development.

Freelance

Android Developer • Freelance, self-employed

April 2017 - December 2018

In April 2017, at the same time as I started learning programming at the basic level, I found my interest in developing mobile applications.

Freelance

Java Software Developer • Freelance, self-employed

April 2017 - December 2018

In April 2017, I started programming with C++ and Java, as a self-taught university academic. I used to do very small and amateur projects on a part-time basis.

Projects



Jeanswest Mobile Application

Jeanswest Mobile Application powered by Flutter(Dart)



Jeanswest Application

Development Backend of Jeanswest Web, Jeanswest Web Application powered by NodeJS

Website:

https://www.jeanswest.ir/

Google Play Application:

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details? id=com.avakatan.club&hl=en_US&gl=US



Balcafe Website

Development Backend of Balcafe Website powered by NodeJS https://balcafe.ir/



Jeanswest STS (Saving Time Service)

Development Backend of Jeanswest STS Machine powered by NodeJS

Project Introduction Video:

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Xyetlqvxw MljjSSrxksdAJ xXLYc5LC6/view?usp=sharing

Education



Kermanshah University Of Technology

Bachelor's degree, Architecture System Computers

2013 - 2018

Skills

